Khoa Nguyen

www.coderfoundry.com/khoanguyen

FRAMEWORKS & PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

HTML5 CSS3 JavaScript/ES6 JQuery

Bootstrap

.NET

C#

MVC

ASP.NET

SQL & Bash

LINQ

Xamarin

WebAPI

React

Node.js

MongoDB

Wordpress



1231 Shields Road, Suite 5 Kernersville, NC 27284 (336) 231-8632

partnerships@coderfoundry.com

This resume contains information furnished by the candidate and has not been independently verified by Coder Foundry, LLC.

This information is privileged, confidential, and to be used solely by the individual and entity to which it has been submitted.

EDUCATION

Santa Ana College, Associates in Business

Santa Ana, CA · 2011

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Coder Foundry, Web Software Engineer

Kernersville, NC · July 2020 – September 2020

- · Created three primary projects, including:
 - 1. A portfolio site using C#, MVC, HTML5, CSS3, BOOTSTRAP, JS & jQuery.
 - 2. A Financial Portal implemented in three phases. Phase 1: an MVC Web Application, Phase 2: a Web Service that utilizes Swagger and Swashbuckle for integrated testing, Phase 3: A cross platform Xamarin Mobile Application.
 - 3. Fully designed and developed a multi-functional issue tracker web application, implementing enhanced roles & security, which also used a Code First Relational database designed and modeled in SQL Server. Technologies used include: .Net Framework v. 4.6.1, MVC5, C#, LINQ, SQL, Entity Framework, jQuery DataTables.

Gadget Parts, Senior Technician

Huntington Beach, CA · May 2014 – October 2019

- Mastered the diagnosing and repairing process for a wide range of computing devices, especially mobile devices.
- Assisted WholeSale accounts.
- Trained new technicians.

Bella Roma Italian Restaurant, Store Manager

Huntington Beach, CA · September 2009 – February 2014

- Responsible for 12 full time employees.
- Managed the kitchen, dining area and delivery drivers.